[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
This is good,
but not as thrilling as riding a horse.
I heard you
smashed the Second Batou's Xuande Jar.
He's quick to talk.
Good job smashing it.
To do big business,
you have to be willing to invest.
What you say makes sense.
Then how about
you add some more capital?
Sure.
What do I get?
I'll get you a new house.
And an American car,
how about that?
So generous?
Sure.
That's wonderful.
So filial.
Who taught you to be so filial?
Your mother or your mentor?
Living under someone else's roof,
I have no choice.
Poor thing.
Wanna try?
[A Prophet]
[Episode 15]
This old eunuch
insists the thumb ring Fifth Master gave us is fake.
And...
What are you looking at me for?
Go on.
Second Master,
he said
the real dragon throne should have a crack underneath,
caused by Emperor Xuantong's kick.
What are you looking at?
How would I know Xuantong kicked the dragon throne?
Second Brother, your craftsmanship is flawless.
Masters,
this eunuch is clearly coming for us.
If he exposes the scam,
we're all doomed.
I told you to pull out, but you didn't.
Now his wife is back to mess things up.
I think
the 70% cut is gone.
t1
Sixth Master,
it's your turn.
Don't boss me around.
I'll settle the score with you
after this game.
Your Majesty.
Madam.
Honey?
Honey, why are you here?
-Greetings, Your Majesty. -Greetings, Your Majesty.
Rise.
You guys put on quite a show.
You bunch of swindlers.
And you—
you little vixen.
I'll make sure you don't leave here alive today.
Watch how I deal with you—
What are you doing?
You're asking me what I'm doing?
Cao San!
You absolute fool.
I brought the eunuch here today.
Your pipe dream is over!
And you swindlers—
none of you will get away!
Madam.
Your Majesty.
You...
Madam.
Calm down.
Let me see.
Back when
the Eight-Nation Alliance entered the capital,
a German barbarian
named Waldersee
acted wildly in the palace.
Not only did he sit on the dragon throne,
but he also had his servants take a photo of him.
In the end, he was decapitated
and died a gruesome death.
He didn't even know how he died.
The authentic Dragon Throne
is a national treasure
that converges
the Three Powers of Heaven, Earth, and Humanity.
It's full of Yang energy.
So,
anyone who usurps the throne
will die a horrible death.
Did you hear that?
A horrible death.
Sect Leader Cao,
if this is the real dragon throne,
I advise you not to touch it.
He is that Eastern dragon!
Quick,
protect the Emperor!
Watch out, Your Majesty!
My beloved concubine.
Cao San.
Doggie,
protect the Emperor!
Honey!
Cao San.
They...
Drop the act.
Let's all go back to the hall.
What are you doing?
There's one we didn't use.
State Preceptor!
Open the door! State Preceptor!
Quick!
State Preceptor!
What happened?
The bed!
Over here.
I'm fine.
Quickly, check if His Majesty
is hurt.
What exactly happened?
Some people suddenly rushed in.
They looked Japanese.
They started shooting right away,
almost hurting His Majesty.
Your Majesty!
Let me check if you're injured.
I'm fine.
Go find a doctor for Miss Jiang
immediately.
No,
that will attract the Japanese.
An assassination attempt
means His Majesty's identity and whereabouts are exposed.
The most important thing now
is to move His Majesty to a safe place.
Your Majesty, your health is the priority.
As your subjects,
it's our duty even if we die.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Exactly.
It's our duty to risk our lives for you,
Your Majesty.
I'm fine.
Duty?
My goodness,
you bunch of frauds.
Your Majesty!
Don't...
Don't get up.
Greetings, Your Majesty...
Get up!
Where did this little street rat come from?
First time seeing you.
You must be the leader of these frauds.
Calm down, Your Majesty.
I am completely loyal to the Emperor.
Still acting in front of me?
You guys really love acting.
If you love it so much,
I'll build a stage for you to act all you want.
And you, you little vixen,
finally showing your true colors.
How dare you steal my man?
Do you know
I saved this man's life?
What are you doing?
Your Majesty,
are you okay?
Enough!
Cao San!
You dare hit me
for this vixen?
She's not a vixen.
Look at
how badly she's hurt for me.
And them—
they are all my loyal subjects.
-Your Majesty is wise. -Your Majesty is wise.
My god...
Oh my goodness!
You've all really gone mad!
Eunuch.
Quick, tell him
they are all frauds.
That dragon throne is fake.
Say something!
Speak up!
Which banner are you from?
I am of the Plain White Banner,
with the Manchu surname Fuca.
Madam,
I've taken a look.
That dragon throne
is real.
It's the very one from the Hall of Supreme Harmony.
Look,
I've been looking at it for over 20 years.
I wouldn't be mistaken.
Impossible.
These people are all scammers.
I just asked them in Manchu,
and they really are Bannermen.
You're in cahoots with them.
You old scammer!
Madam,
you asked me to come and appraise it for you.
I was in the palace for over 20 years.
Even the masters couldn't bear
to lay a finger on me.
And you actually...
All right.
Even the eunuch you found
said the throne was real.
What else is there to say?
Can't you wish me well?
How can I make you Empress
when you're acting like this?
Your Majesty.
Don't pull me!
Your Majesty, please stop arguing.
Her Majesty
is just unable to accept this so suddenly.
Please don't blame her.
Get away, you little vixen!
I'll kill you.
Still seducing him, huh?
Are you trying to rebel?
How dare you hit me!
Someone!
Summon the imperial physician for me!
Cao San!
You're ridiculous!
Calm down, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
It's done.
Scammer.
Miss Jiang,
I need you to promise me.
You must recover well.
State Preceptor.
I'm leaving Miss Jiang in your care.
You must cure her.
Rest assured, Your Majesty.
Cao San, come out!
You blockhead.
You've lost your mind.
I haven't even ascended the throne yet,
and the harem is already this noisy.
My beloved concubine,
recover well.
I will come see you again tomorrow.
Your Majesty,
don't worry.
I didn't expect
this gold-lacquered carved dragon throne really has the aura of a true dragon.
I said it had a crack,
and it actually did.
May I ask, Eunuch,
what do you mean by that?
I deliberately said
that the dragon throne had a crack.
Those who don't know better
would think this dragon throne
is made of golden thread nanmu.
But the main material of the dragon throne
is brass.
Can a child really crack
a gold-painted brass dragon chair with a kick?
You bunch of frauds.
You're still not taking it seriously.
Whether we're taking it seriously or not
depends on if you can
walk out that door today.
What?
You're going to kill me?
Fine.
Once I die,
it won't be long
before Cao San figures it out.
Trading my old life with one foot in the grave
for yours
is worth it.
Old sir,
why...
are you doing this?
Very simple.
Let's make a deal.
Interested?
What kind of deal?
Help me kill Cao San.
Eunuch,
this will
start a blood feud with the Beggar Sect.
I am a eunuch
with no sons or daughters.
I went back to my hometown and adopted 2 children.
A few years ago, I took them to the street,
and they suddenly went missing.
I searched for a long time but couldn't find them.
A few months ago, I saw them
begging on the street.
They were completely crippled!
Dirty work like this
was done by Cao San and his gang.
I just want to see those bastards
go to hell with my own eyes.
Then you could just find a chance
to trade your life for his.
Why drag us into this?
Since we have a common enemy,
then we are friends now.
This is a deal
then.
It's a deal.
Shangguan Chengming.
Since ancient times,
Tianxiang Sect has been setting things up
to make money.
At first,
you wanted to sell fake treasures to make money.
I gave you the Xuande Jar without a second thought,
right?
Then,
the jar was smashed, and I didn't see a single dime.
And then,
you wanted to sell some pipe dream.
Fine.
I made a dragon throne for you.
Now,
you want to destroy the Beggar Sect.
Let me ask you,
are you playing us for fools?
It's a pity if you don't lie to a fool.
Calm down,
Second Master.
How could this scam not make money?
C-Cut the crap.
Compensate me for the Xuande Jar first.
I will after we finish this.
Do it yourself if you want.
I quit.
Second Brother.
Hey—
Sixth Brother, why don't we just
call off this scam?
If Shangguan Chengming keeps making trouble,
I'm afraid he'll drag down the whole Tianxiang Sect.
If anything goes wrong,
how can we explain it to the Sect Master?
Makes sense.
Since all the Batous want to stop,
let's call off
this scam.
Then wouldn't all the money we spent before
be wasted?
How could it be wasted?
Not at all.
It's all on your tab.
Brother,
forget about the emperor.
It's over.
What should we do, bro?
Why aren't you anxious at all?
They've left. With just us, we won't be able to do it.
Now that you have absolute confidence,
you kicked everyone out immediately.
What a tight plan.
You know me so well now?
So that's what it is.
Kick them all out so we can make more money.
He doesn't care about money at all.
Of course I do.
I have such a huge debt.
You can...
-go to Miss Chen in Pangzhou— -Hey!
Why didn't I think of that?
You have a
rich friend, Miss Chen, in Pangzhou.
Ask her for help.
We're just regular friends.
How could I have the nerve to ask her?
If the friend in Pangzhou won't do,
you can find the one in Pujiang.
If not Pujiang, isn't there one in Suzhou?
Anyway, you have many friends.
You don't have to worry about having no one to back you up.
It also saves us
from working for nothing.
Don't go.
I'm counting on you now.
You still have Liang.
Right.
I will protect you.
Let me go!
Dakui, Erkui,
how dare you arrest me!
Be gentle, you two.
Let me go!
I'm not going in!
Give me the keys!
Erkui!
Let me go!
Sorry, Madam.
Dakui, give me the keys!
Did you hear me, you two?
Cao,
you ungrateful bastard!
Back then,
if it weren't for my dad,
you would've been turned into a human dog!
Let me out!
When will you be
as clear-headed
as I am?
Then I'll let you out.
Cao, let me out!
My surname is Aisin Gioro.
Aisin Gioro, you blockhead!
You're the blockhead!
Let me out!
Master,
from the eunuch.
[Your Majesty, it's dangerous out there now. Please secretly head to Yunhe Temple tomorrow; I have important matters to report.]
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty,
finding you and serving you
makes my life complete.
Look.
This...
Hurry up.
Let's go.
Your Majesty,
your mansion
is besieged on all sides.
Mr. Shangguan,
in order to stabilize all forces,
disguised himself as you
and continues to live in the residence
to control the situation.
This is what we call
advancing secretly while feigning a retreat.
Your Majesty is wise.
For now, just treat this Yunhe Temple
as your temporary palace.
What if there's another
assassination attempt at the old residence?
Doggie will lead a team
to guard day and night.
I'm afraid
my wife...
Your Majesty, that's exactly what I was about to ask.
Do you want to invite
Her Majesty here as well?
Eunuch,
what do you think?
To say something treasonous,
the less people know
of this place, the safer.
It's better Her Majesty...
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
You may rise.
As for my beloved consort,
how is she recovering from her injuries?
Rest assured, Your Majesty.
Miss Jiang is being well taken care of.
She also instructed me,
saying that Your Majesty loves...
loves to drink this.
Have a cup.
No,
put this down first.
Put it down there.
My beloved consort, she is so thoughtful.
Your Majesty,
you have finished washing up.
We are ready to dress you.
All right.
Please take a look, Your Majesty.
For me?
Yes, Your Majesty.
It is yours.
Mine?
Is this real?
Your Majesty,
all land under heaven belongs to you,
and all people are your subjects.
Who would dare to fake your dragon robe?
I have liked yellow color since I was a child.
Yes.
You will like it even more once you are dressed in it.
[A now extinguished fire broke out in Yimin Alley at night. Fortunately, there are no casualties.]
What?
The old house is on fire?
Let me take a look.
Please calm down, Your Majesty.
I will go check the situation
and report back to you.
Your Majesty!
Lingyu!
The fire at the mansion last night
must have been set intentionally.
I saw
many many men in black
broke into the room.
Mr. Shangguan...
What happened to him?
Mr. Shangguan,
with his last breath,
entrusted me
to hand this letter to you personally.
He said only with his death
would those villains truly be at ease.
[For His Majesty's personal receipt]
Long live Your Majesty.
The 29 armies in Peiping
have all been arranged.
Please ensure you depart tomorrow night.
This check
is all we loyal subjects
have.
To have helped you ascend the throne,
I die without regrets.
Your Majesty.
My State Preceptor...
Your Majesty,
please take care of yourself.
Only if you successfully ascend the throne
will the State Preceptor's sacrifice
be meaningful.
How is
the Empress?
Rest assured, Your Majesty.
Her Majesty
has been safely moved to a civilian residence,
completely unharmed.
For the sake of the big picture,
I believe
it is best for Your Majesty and the Empress
to return to Peiping separately.
Yes,
Miss Jiang is absolutely right.
How about this, Your Majesty?
You write a letter to Her Highness
explaining the current situation.
Also,
have her cash this draft
at the bank and deposit it
under your name.
That works.
Lingyu risked her life
to get this check back.
I shall let Lingyu
handle it for me.
As you command, Your Majesty.
Please write
a letter of authorization
yourself, Your Majesty.
Bring me brush and ink.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I shall entrust
this heavy responsibility to you.
Rest assured, Your Majesty.
Miss Jiang,
you have to come back immediately
after cashing this check.
Tomorrow night, you and the Fifth Master will accompany
His Majesty to the Imperial City.
I obey your command.
Eunuch,
what about you?
I'm leaving tonight
to set up security at the station.
For Your Majesty's ascension,
everything must be foolproof.
This is the letter of authorization written by Cao San himself.
It is indeed exactly the same.
It seems you have learned quite a lot these past 2 years.
This is for Lao Yang.
This is for Cao San's wife.
Why are you here?
Please calm down, Madam.
[To: Madam]
[Check]
As the saying goes,
the Emperor guards the nation's gates,
and the monarch dies for the state.
His Majesty ascending the throne
is a matter of national importance.
We seek your understanding
of His Majesty's good intentions.
Eunuch,
do you also think
he is the Emperor?
Who sent you?
It was the Sect Leader.
The Sect Leader?
Yes.
Impossible.
You... You are talking nonsense.
How could the Sect Leader ask you to kill me?
The Sect Leader...
He told me to kill you, Madam.
Words are no proof.
I...
I have a letter.
[To: Yang]
Madam.
Impossible.
Cao San would never
send someone to kill me.
Madam.
I have been in the palace for many years.
The dragon throne
is not for any mortal.
That dragon throne is extremely cold.
The heart of the one who sits on it
is even
colder than it.
Cao San and I
have been married
for over 20 years.
How could he bear to kill me?
When he had no food as a child,
I was the one who fed him.
When the old Sect Leader almost turned him into a human dog,
my father saved him.
How could he be so cruel?
How could he kill me?
Impossible.
Madam,
you can draw a tiger's skin, but not its bones.
You may know a person's face, but not their heart.
Cao San...
How is it?
The money is gone.
It's all... gone?
Before you arrived,
Mr. Cao's men withdrew the money.
This is Mr. Cao's authorization letter.
The account and password are on it.
This darn Cao San.
How could he draw all the money?
This dog.
He'll rot in hell.
He'll rot!
Let's go
to the police station.
[Shunxiang Teahouse]
Are all the people in here clean?
These are all your subjects.
I didn't want to make such a big scene,
but the Japanese
have weapons.
Your Majesty, the train leaves tonight.
Once we reach Peiping,
you will be the true Son of Heaven.
Your Majesty, please rest here for now.
Play some cards and have some tea.
Your Majesty,
Fifth Master and I
will go arrange your schedule.
I'll come back to pick you up
in 4 hours.
I shall take my leave.
Wait.
When this is done,
I promise you a position below only one
and above all others.
Thank you for your grace, Your Majesty!
Rise.
And you, Miss Jiang.
You saved my life.
By then,
I'll make you the Noble Consort.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
But Your Majesty,
I do not seek such titles.
I only wish to stay by your side.
Serving you well
is more than enough for me.
History
will remember today.
-Long live the Emperor! -Long live the Emperor!
Go on with your work.
-Yes, Your Majesty. -Yes, Your Majesty.
Chief,
what did you mean
by catching them in a trap today?
Cao San?
You are...
I am Wang Zhicheng,
Chief of the Yucheng Police Department.
With you protecting me,
I can rest easy.
In the future,
you'll be my Nine Gates' Infantry Commander.
You're here to...
Have fun with the people.
Do you know how to play mahjong?
Come on, let's play.
You know, governing a great nation
is like cooking a small fish,
it must be done slowly.
These days,
it's been hard for me to eat or sleep.
After I ascend the throne,
I will govern with all my might.
Take Yucheng, for example.
The public order is a total mess.
The economy is failing too.
The atmosphere is foul.
This is highly improper.
Kong.
South Wind.
Nine Gates' Infantry Commander.
What's wrong?
I've won.
Good hand.
It's all yours.
But you must
protect Her Majesty well.
No matter what,
Her Majesty is going to Peiping with me.
She can't live without me.
Rest assured,
Her Majesty is with us.
You will see her
very soon.
Good, good.
But,
Her Majesty must have complained a lot to you, right?
She said everything she should.
Only believe half of what a woman says.
Her Majesty said
you really killed
the old Sect Leader.
That was a long time ago.
What else did Her Majesty tell you?
I heard
you chopped off that old geezer's head
with your own hands,
and hung it in the hall for 3 days.
I had to chop it off myself.
The Beggar Sect must have its rules.
How ruthless.
Ordinary people couldn't do that.
You are my historian, right?
Yes.
Then write it down in detail.
A while ago, Lincheng's Beggar Gang leader came to make trouble.
And you put him in his place.
You even know that?
I was right there.
Then I have to ask you.
Did you see
how I did it?
Unfortunately, I didn't see that with my own eyes.
Write this down.
At that time, 18 men by the river
wanted to steal my empire.
I took 2 short sabers,
and slashed from one end of the street to the other.
The sabers...
were all chipped.
The ground was covered in blood.
It squelched when you stepped on it.
Guess why I wasn't hurt?
Why?
Highlight this part.
It's because of the scar on my back—
it's the dragon vein!
Isn't that the scar left
by the old Sect Leader
when he tried to mutilate you into a human dog?
Insolent!
What do you mean?
What do you all mean?
Are you trying to rebel?
Brilliant.
The Japanese
would never have thought
we would put on an act
like this to escape.
Who came up with this?
This is too brilliant.
Right, if we're acting, let's do the full set.
Don't just stand there.
Who has handcuffs?
Hurry up and cuff me.
Cuff him.
Hurry!
I'll do it myself.
What a great trick
of advancing secretly.
Come on.
Arrest me.
Escort me to Peiping.
He talks too much.
Take him down.
Take him away.
Such a big scene.
This isn't just putting on an act.
This is putting on a full act.
I am the Emperor.
You know that, right?
And I'm the Lord of Heaven.
Kneel properly!
I have to say,
these guys are acting pretty well.
Li Mazi,
guilty of murder,
arson,
rape of women.
Punished for multiple crimes,
he is sentenced to death by shooting—
to be executed immediately.
Wang Dabao, guilty of murder
and burglary.
Punished for multiple crimes,
he is sentenced to death by shooting—
to be executed immediately.
Peng Sanchuan, guilty of banditry,
murder,
robbery,
and rape.
He is sentenced to death by shooting—
to be executed immediately.
Liars!
You're all liars!
How could I be scammed?
I am the Emperor!
I wonder if Mr. Cao's General Longxiang
is for sale?
Greetings.
And this is?
I can only tell you
his surname is Aisin Gioro.
You're interested in this item?
What you see may not be real.
What you see is real.
To see the mystery,
the hidden dragon must reveal itself.
Long live the Emperor!
Did something grow
on Sect Leader Cao's back?
What grew?
The dragon vein.
It appeared!
This is simply the will of Heaven!
The dragon vein is finally continued.
The Great Qing will not fall!
The heavy responsibility of restoring the Qing Dynasty
now rests in your hands.
When we get to Peiping,
you will be the true Son of Heaven.
Cao San,
guilty of murder,
child abuse,
false imprisonment,
and instigating theft.
The facts of the crimes are clear,
and the evidence is irrefutable.
Upon trial by the Yucheng Court,
you are sentenced
to death by shooting
and deprived of political rights for life—
to be executed immediately.
I am truly the only one who sees things clearly.
Here's the deed to the three-courtyard house in the west of the city.
The car is parked in the backyard.
Everything promised before
has been settled.
Good job.
Why does it feel like something is missing?
I remember now.
There are 13 boxes of silver coins
in Cao San’s warehouse.
Where is the money?
In your name,
it was all donated to an orphanage.
What did you say?
The first rule of our Tianxiang Sect is
unlawful money
should be scattered in natural disasters.
Bullshit!
The brothers of our Tianxiang Sect
risk their lives to make money,
not to do charity.
Shouldn't the Tianxiang Sect be robbing the rich to help the poor?
It's a good donation.
This orphanage
is better than 12 boxes of silver dollars.
Thank you all for your strong support.
Nanxi Orphanage opens today.
For the homeless children,
I thank you all.
[Nanxi Orphanage Opening Ceremony]
Nanxi...
Why did you name
the orphanage this?
Is there a story behind it?
Yanzi, I smashed the Xuande Jar for you,
and I have no regrets.
You brat.
Let's settle our scores later.
Second Batou,
have you forgotten?
Cao San still has some authentic pieces.
I didn't expect
he would really succeed.
I thought he was just a greenhorn,
but he turned out to be a nuisance.
A nuisance?
I actually find him quite interesting.
The Sect Master placed a troublemaker in the hall.
Do you think he's being smart,
or is he just getting senile?
You've found a kindred spirit.
When you are lost in the darkness,
look to the light.
When you've been in the dark for too long,
someone has to crack it open
to let the light in.
Hey,
I just remembered.
Why didn't the old eunuch who helped us come?
He leaves after the deed is done,
seeking neither fame nor credit.
The eunuch is indeed
a man of hidden talents.
It's just a small trick.
It must be a joke to you.
Steady now.
Don't bite off more than you can chew,
and don't act before the time is right.
I couldn't ask for more than to join forces
with the Fifth Batou.
Join forces?
I'm here too.
Don't forget about Liang.
Right.
You still have Liang.
For your
Liang,
stay alive
in our Tianxiang Sect.
What you did
is truly a heroic act
benefiting the country and the people.
That's not quite right.
We must credit your brilliance
for catching that beast, Cao San.
Otherwise, how many more children would have suffered?
Don't you agree?
Since I met Sect Leader,
things have been going smoothly.
Rest assured.
From now on, in this territory,
we are in this
together.
[In the next episode]
Are you human?
Have you no humanity?
People like Tang Yushan
aren't scared of ghosts and deities.
They won't buy it.
He's not afraid of ghosts
because he's never seen ghosts before.
To seek justice for a dead person—
is it worth it?
I'll
accept this round.